idea / Apple I'll be actually recording
this crap in the white light at the top
so I come here to the numbers movie it's
also blinking red though so that's an
indication Apple number 25 is lgbtq+
friendly sex ed classes online because
if we care that deeply that their school
systems in different parts of the world
aren't adequately teaching it we can
create it ourselves what would we have
wanted as teenagers to know about our
bodies and sexuality and gender when we
were preteens and teens and then
creating that content I'm playing it
online in musical way
I mean stuffs out there it's on YouTube
but creating an actual course that
someone can go through and discover who
they are and how to best be themselves
well 25 lgbt-friendly
online sex it corpses it just rolls off
the time